# John Woolbright

1326 San Jacinto CT, St. Louis, MO 63139

Phone: 314-604-3316 Email: <a href="mailto:jwoolbright23@gmail.com">jwoolbright23@gmail.com</a>

Github: github.com/jwoolbright23

#### **Skills**

Programming Languages: Operating Systems: Software:

Python Mac OS VScode

Java Windows IntelliJ IDE

### Summary

Passionate, organized, and versatile worker with proficiency in computer coding, customer service, and coordination. Skilled at working with both Java and Python programming languages. Experienced at accomplishing multiple tasks at once, making deadlines, and promoting a positive work environment.

### **Personal Project**

I am currently working on an Inventory based web-application. This application will allow you to have your very own user account while also being able to create and manage your own inventory. The app will focus on Angular and Springboot frameworks.

#### Education

Coding Certificate - LaunchCode LC101 Kansas City, MO

2018-2019

LaunchCode is a coding program that teaches core fundamentals for software development.

**High School Diploma** - St. John Vianney High School St. Louis, MO

2005-2009

## **Professional Experience**

**Warehouse Framing Coordinator** – New West Frame & Moulding Kansas City, MO *2018-Present* Work operating machinery to cut and join frames.

**Framing Sales Representative and Coordinator -** Dogtown Sports Collectibles and Framing St. Louis, MO

2015-2018

Worked in a sports collectibles shop specializing in customized framing. Participated actively in all steps of the process including assembly, purchasing, and selling of products. In addition, operated heavy machinery to cut frames and mats.

Sales Representative - Fox River Dairy St. Louis, MO

2013-2015

Worked as a sales representative selling all retail products and coordinating with customers to secure a smooth sales operation.

Warehouse and Distribution Management - Fox River Dairy St. Louis, MO

2011-2013

Worked in a warehouse environment handling the day to day operations including customer billing, driver routing, and shipping and receiving company orders.

References Available upon Request